Don't Hold Back ...Don't Give Up.
Raise Your Voice is a music, drama, romance film directed by Sean McNamara.
A coming-of-age story centered around a small-town singer brokenhearted by the death of her brother in a car crash,
who had secretly submitted her for a summer session at a performing arts academy in Los Angeles.
In the academy, she experiences a whole new way of life in the big
city, far from the small town lifestyle she's used to.
Teresa 'Terri' Fletcher, played by Hilary Duff.
Jay Corgan, played by Oliver James.
Simon Fletcher, played by David Keith.
Engelbert  "Kiwi" Wilson, played by Johnny Lewis.
Francis Fletcher, played by Rita Wilson.
Denise Gilmore, played by Dana Davis.
Raise Your Voice is a 2004 American teen musical drama film
directed by Sean McNamara and starring Hilary Duff.
The film received negative reviews and grossed $14.9
million against a $15 million budget.
Three songs by Duff were featured in Raise Your Voice, all of
which appear on her eponymous third album.
"Someone's Watching Over Me" is performed by her
character during the film's climax.
Canadian rock band Three Days Grace makes a cameo appearance in the
film, performing the songs "Are You Ready" and "Home".
The film explores themes of life's dream, aspiring
singer, singer, death of brother, grieving.
The tone is emotional.